{
  "category": "Hiding and Showing Panes in VSCode",
  "quiz": [
    {
      "question": "Toggle Sidebar Visibility",
      "answer": "Ctrl+j S",
      "note": "Show or hide the sidebar"
    },
    {
      "question": "Toggle Panel Visibility",
      "answer": "Ctrl+j B",
      "note": "Show or hide the panel (output, debug console, terminal, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "Toggle Integrated Terminal",
      "answer": "Ctrl+j T",
      "note": "Show or hide the integrated terminal"
    },
    {
      "question": "Toggle Full Screen",
      "answer": "F11",
      "note": "Switch between full screen and normal mode"
    },
    {
      "question": "Toggle Zen Mode",
      "answer": "Ctrl+j Z",
      "note": "Switch between Zen Mode (distraction free mode) and normal mode"
    },
    {
      "question": "Focus on Editor Group",
      "answer": "Ctrl+1 / Ctrl+2 / Ctrl+3",
      "note": "Focus on the first, second, or third editor group"
    },
    {
      "question": "Focus on Sidebar",
      "answer": "Ctrl+0",
      "note": "Focus on the sidebar"
    },
    {
      "question": "Show Debug Console",
      "answer": "Ctrl+j D",
      "note": "Show Debug Console"
    },
    {
      "question": "Show Output Panel",
      "answer": "Ctrl+j o",
      "note": "Focus on the Output Panel"
    },
    {
      "question": "Show Problems Panel",
      "answer": "Ctrl+j p",
      "note": "Focus on the Problems Panel"
    },
    {
      "question": "Maximize Editor Group",
      "answer": "Ctrl+j e",
      "note": "maximize the editor group"
    },
    {
      "question": "Maximize Bottom Panel",
      "answer": "Ctrl+j x",
      "note": "Maximize Bottom Panel"
    },
    {
      "question": "Cycle Bottom Panel",
      "answer": "Ctrl+j Ctrl+j",
      "note": "Focus on the Bottom Panel"
    },
    {
      "question": "Cycle Side Panel",
      "answer": "Ctrl+J Ctrl+S",
      "note": "Cycle the side Panel"
    },
    {
      "question": "nextEditor",
      "answer": "ctrl+pagedown",
      "note": "workbench.action.nextEditor"
    },
    {
      "question": "previousEditor",
      "answer": "ctrl+pageUp",
      "note": "workbench.action.previousEditor"
    },
    {
      "question": "Cycle Editor",
      "answer": "Ctrl+E Ctrl+N",
      "note": "Cycle the EditorsPanel"
    },
    {
      "question": "workbench.action.gotoSymbol",
      "answer": "ctrl+shift+o",
      "note": "Go to Symbol in Editor..."
    },
    {
      "question": "workbench.action.experimental.quickTextSearch",
      "answer": "ctrl+q ctrl+s",
      "note": "Quick Search experimental "
    },
    {
      "question": "workbench.action.quickOpenPreviousRecentlyUsedEditorInGroup",
      "answer": "ctrl+tab",
      "note": "View: Quick Open Previous Recently Used Editor in Group"
    }
    
  ]
}